kissld.com 2012-03-20

# Covista

**Your Personal Information Is Safe With Us**

KISS and Covista Communications work hard to protect the privacy of your personal information.

Click on the links below for more information:

Personally Identifiable Information  
How We Use Information  
How We Collect Information   
Security  
Your Access to Information   
Customer Proprietary Network Information

**Personally Identifiable Information**

Covista does not share, disclose or sell any personally identifiable information (such as your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address) collected online on the Covista site. Should Covista decide to share such data with third parties in the future, we will contact you and get your permission first. 

This information is critical to our business and as such, it would be treated like our other assets in the context of a merger, sale or other corporate reorganization or legal proceeding. 

Covista does not market to or knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.

Return to the Top **How We Use Information**

Covista uses the information we collect online principally to provide you with the service you have ordered and to inform you of other offerings that you may find interesting. Postal and e-mail address information enable us to communication with you about services offered and ordered, as well as the proper provisioning and billing of those services.

Covista may use third-party vendors to carry out certain functions in marketing and delivering services to you (such as processing data files and sending you new order fulfillment information), and so shares online data with those vendors to the extent necessary for them to perform their work. Such partners and vendors must use that personally identifiable information only for the purpose(s) for which it was shared and protect it from any further use. Covista also shares such information with other industry and credit-related organizations to improve operations and to protect against fraud, security and credit risks.

We also provide personally identifiable online information in response to subpoenas and other legal demands, and where we believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against individuals who may be endangering public safety or interfering with Covista property or services. 

Return to the Top

**How We Collect Information**

Covista collects information online and other by asking you for it. A customer's name, address (postal and e-mail) and telephone number are the most important pieces of information, but we might request other information, based on, for example, the service(s) being ordered or promoted.

Covista may also use "cookies" and similar technology to obtain information about your visits to our sites or your responses to email from us - both individually and in aggregated data that does not identify you. These reporting tools tell us the parts of our Web site or emails in which you showed an interest or took some action, and help us improve the quality and usefulness of our sites.

At Covista, we primarily use cookies to determine what services or promotions you are interested in. While cookies help us improve your experience while visiting our site and customize our communications to the services you may desire, you have the option to block them through your internet browser or other commercially available software. However, doing so may make some of our site's features unavailable to you.

Another way in which we collect information online is through our affinity program partners who may provide us with information they have already obtained from you online or other. For example, when you are on a partner's site and click on a Covista banner that takes you to the Covista site, information that the partner has received from you already may be passed to Covista. 

Return to the Top

**Security**

We use encryption, firewalls and other technology and security procedures to help protect the accuracy and security of your personal information and prevent unauthorized access or improper use. For example, you will note that while using some features of the Covista website and online services, you will need to submit a password or some other type of authenticating information.

Return to the Top

**Your Access to Information**

You may review or update the available personally identifiable information that we received from you online by accessing your account online, by contacting Consumer Service at (1-800-323-6875), or through the company contact information below. Please note that in order to better protect you and safeguard your information, we take steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections to your information.

Covista may use e-mail addresses that you provide to us to send you information related to Covista products and services. If at any time you would prefer not to receive further marketing communications, please contact Customer Service at (1-800-323-6875).

Return to the Top

**Customer Proprietary Network Information**

"Customer Proprietary Network Information," or "CPNI" is a broad term that encompasses two main categories of information which carriers like Covista collect and use in order to conduct business and offer telephone and data services. First, CPNI includes, among other things, individually identifiable information indicating to whom, where, and when a customer places a call, as well as the types of service offerings to which a customer subscribes and how much any particular service is used. Second, "aggregate customer" information, is collective data that relates to a group or category of service or customers from which individual customer characteristics have been removed. 

**Collection, Use and Disclosure**

Typically, companies like Covista collect the data described above through the ordinary course of the customer-carrier relationship. When necessary, Covista uses such information to fulfill orders, provide service, bill, and communicate with customers. We may also use such data to develop new products or services tailored to fit customers' specific needs.

Covista protects all CPNI in the control of Covista, and treats such information in a manner consistent and in compliance with Federal Communications Commission (FCC) requirements. 

Return to the Top

**"Individually Identifiable" CPNI**

Covista will not sell, trade, or disclose to unaffiliated third parties any individually identifiable customer information without the consent of the customer. As used in this Privacy Policy, "unaffiliated third parties" do not include Covista's agents or affiliates that sell or provide communications-related services, its joint venture partners, or independent contractors. 

However, Covista, its agents and affiliates that provide communications-related services, its joint venture partners or independent contractors may use, disclose, or permit unaffiliated third parties to access customers' individually identifiable CPNI in order to (1) initiate, render, bill, and collect for telecommunications service; (2) protect Covista's rights or property, or to protect customers and other carriers from the fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful use of, or subscription to, such service; or (3) to provide any inbound telemarketing, referral, or administrative service to the customer for the duration of the call, if such call was initiated by the customer and the customer approves of the use of such information to provide such service.

Please note that in order to better serve your communications needs and to identify, offer and provide products and services to meet your requirements, we need your permission to share this information among our affiliates and agents and their subsidiaries. The protection of your information is important to us, and we acknowledge that you have a right, and we have a duty, under federal and state law, to protect the confidentiality of your CPNI. 

You have a right to keep your CPNI private by "opting out." Unless you provide us with notice that you wish to opt out within 30 days of us providing notice to you in your bill or through the mail, we will assume that you give us the right to share your CPNI with the authorized companies as described above. CPNI will not be shared with unrelated third parties. You may opt out by calling us at 1-800-323-6875.

Return to the Top

**"Aggregate Customer" Information**

Covista also gathers a variety of aggregate customer information, including, but not limited to, the number and frequency of calls into our Customer Care Department and visits to Covista's website and its different pages. Web visits are monitored through the use of "cookies." A cookie is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain websites. Covista may use cookies to collect, store, and sometimes track information for statistical purposes to improve the products and service we provide and to manage our telecommunications networks. As explained in more detail below, Covista may share with unaffiliated third parties such aggregate information.

Non-Covista websites may require you to accept cookies. We do not control use of these cookies and expressly disclaim responsibility for information collected through them.

Return to the Top
